http://www.acmehowto.com/admin/privacy.php

Q & A Forums
DISCLOSURE: This post may contain affiliate links, meaning when you click the links, we may receive a commission.
Newsletter
Sign up to receive our free Maintenance Reminder Newsletter
Learn More
Privacy Statement for
Acme How To.com,
Acme DIY.com
and
Acme Parts.com
Before the legalese - We here at Acme are people just like you and just like you we don't want our personal information	abused by anyone. In that spirit, we try to gather as little personal information, about you as an individual, as possible. We do gather data and compile it so we can create statistical reports and graphs. Any personal information we may have about you is used internally. We don't send you email or anything else, unless you signed up to receive it. If you ever want to stop receiving email from us, the email includes an easy to find and use Unsubscribe link. Forums users can stop email from within their forum account. We do work with other companies, such as advertisers, and they may collect their own data. Please read their privacy policies for information about them and their practices. Now back to the lawyers.
ACME PARTS.com, Inc. has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: ACME PARTS.com, ACME HOW TO.com and ACME DIY.com
We are committed to protecting your privacy. We use any information we collect about you to process orders and to provide a better web experience. It is our policy to never share information of a financial or personal nature that identifies an individual, with any entity outside of ACME PARTS.com, Inc. and its companies unless compelled by force of law. We do share information on an aggregated or statistical basis.
Our web site logs IP addresses and browser types to gather broad demographic information, but we do not link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable. This means that a user's session will be tracked, but the user will be anonymous. Your IP address may be used to help identify your shopping cart or log-on session.
Our site may use cookies to keep track of your shopping cart,
to deliver content specific to your interests, to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site, and for other user experience related purposes.
Our site's registration forms may require users to give us contact information (such as their name and e-mail address) and demographic information (such as their zip code, age, or income level). We use customer contact information from the registration forms to send the user requested information. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data for other purposes. We use this data to tailor the visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis.
ACME PARTS.com does not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others. We may choose to do so in the future with trustworthy third parties, but you can tell us not to by sending a blank e-mail message to
. (If you use more than one e-mail address to shop with us, send this message from each e-mail account you use.) Also, ACME PARTS.com may provide aggregate statistics about our customers, sales, traffic patterns, and related site information to reputable third-party vendors, but these statistics will include no personally identifying information.
This site contains links to other sites. ACME PARTS.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.
Our site uses an order form for customers to request information, products, and services. We collect visitor's contact information (like their mail address) and financial information (like their account or credit card numbers). Contact information from the order form is used to send orders to our customers. The customer's contact information is used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Financial information that is collected is used to bill the user for products and services.Our online surveys ask visitors for demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis.We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information.
We use third-party companies to serve ads and collect non-personally identifiable information (e.g., the pages you visit, and which links you click, which ads you see and click on, and the categories of search terms you enter) when you visit our web site. These companies may use the information outlined above (which does NOT include your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. These companies often use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here (link to the NAI universal user opt-out).
Public Forums
This site does or may make chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. Security
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. When you place orders or access your account information, we offer the use of a secure server. The secure server software (SSL) encrypts all information you input before it is sent to us. Furthermore, all of the customer data we collect is protected against unauthorized access.
Choice/Opt-Out
Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us
at the point where we request information about the visitor.
This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service.
You 		can send mail to
Correct/Update
This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided.
You can send mail to
Your Consent
By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by ACME PARTS.com If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.
Contacting the Web Site
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact
Policy Administration
ACME PARTS.com, Inc.
27862 Via Corita
Los Altos, CA 94022
Search for Articles on Acme How To
Home | Privacy | Contact Acme | Legal | Advertise
Copyright © 2000 - 2020, Acme Parts.com, Inc. All rights reserved. Contact us to obtain licensing.Use of this site is subject to certain Terms of use which constitute a legal agreement between you and Acme Parts.com, Inc.
